

### Contact











+7 918 98 65 56 8



Russia, Temruk



✓ Steelmen87@bk.ru



My portfolio

# **Expertise**

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Redux / Redux-Toolkit
- Redux Thunk
- Material UI
- CCS3 / SASS / HTML5
- Rest API / Axios
- Formik / React Hook Form
- Postman
- UnitTest / TDD
- Storybook
- Git / GitHub

## Languages

English - B1 (in progress)

Russian - native

# Petrov Konstantin

### Front-end Developer

Hello, I am a person who has a strong passion for programming. I have experience creating a SPA using React/Redux/TypeScript. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with the help of new technologies such as react native. I spend my free time improving my English and solving problems on Codewars. I am open to your suggestions.

## **Experience**

### MY PROJECTS AS FRONT-END DEVELOPER (Part-Time)

#### **OTRAINING CARDS**

november 2022 - present

Start-up project, Part time

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Formik, Material-UI. Using TypeScript for better code control, ESLint, Prettier for the best code style. Organizing correct app arcitecture. Team development: bug fixing, refactoring, deploying.

#### O SOCIAL NETWORK

march 2021 - june 2022

Self-education project, Part time

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Redux-form, Ant Design, Reselect. Using TypeScript for better code control, ESLint, Prettier for the best code style. Creating unit tests, bug fixing, refactoring, deploying. Organizing correct app arcitecture.

#### O TODO LIST

august 2022 - november

2022 Educational project

Stack: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Material-UI. Using TypeScript for better code control. Covering code with unit tests, bug fixing, refactoring, deploying.

### **Automated Control System Engineer (Full-Time)**

#### O 2018 - 2022

- Programming of controllers
- Design and implementation of automated process control systems
- Preparation of applications for the purchase of equipment
- Checking the operability of the object in the SCADA dispatch control system

## **Education**

2021-2022 | IT-INCUBATOR (React, Redux, TS, JS)

**Front-end Development** 

2005-2010 | RUSSIAN STATE SOCIAL UNIVERSITY

**Automated Control System Engineer**